>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，继续我们的探索
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, so
continuing on with our exploration of this
原型模式。
prototype pattern.
如果我要去的话就像我在第 10 行
If I were to, as I'm doing on line 10,
请获取该 deepJS 对象并向其添加请求。
take that deepJS object and
add an ask to it.
在第 10 行中，我将直接向 deepJS 添加一个请求。
See on line 10,
I'm adding an ask directly to deepJS.
记住，创建的第 4 行在 workshop.prototype上。
Remember, the one that's created,
line 4, is up on workshop.prototype.
我在 deepJS 对象上制作另一个相同的名称。
And I'm making another one of
the same name on the deepJS object.
如果你能想象到你脑袋里的那张图
And if you can visualize to
that diagram in your head,
那就意味着我们有了阴暗的阴影
then that means that we
have shadowing going on.
我们有两个不同层次的原型链
Cuz we have two different
levels of the prototype chain
拥有完全相同的财产
with the exact same property.
我在 11 号线路上说
When I say on line 11 this.ask,
该关键字在第 11 行上的意义是什么 ?
what is the this keyword
gonna point at on line 11?
此时，每当我问你，这个关键词会指向什么 ?
At this point, whenever I ask you,
what is the this keyword gonna point at?
您的缺省响应应该是，呼叫站点在哪里 ?
Your default response should be,
where's the call-site?
这里的呼叫地点在哪里
So where is the call-site here?
那是什么线
What line is it on?
>> 扬声器 2: 14?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: 14?
>> Kyle Simpson: 第 14 行，第 14 行的呼叫站点告知
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Line 14, and
what does line 14's call-site tell
关于此关键字将在该方法调用中的内容吗 ?
us about what the this keyword will
be inside of that method call?
还记得隐式绑定规则吗 ?
Remember the implicit binding rule?
这是所有规则中最重要的
That's the most important
of all the rules,
它告诉我们这个关键词会指向深度 JS
it tells us that this keyword
is gonna point at deepJS.
因此，在第 11 行中，这是 deepJS。
So on line 11, this is deepJS.
因此，我们现在说的是加深联署材料的问题。
So we are now saying deepJS.ask, again.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 那接下来会发生什么呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what's gonna happen?
无限的递归对吧
And infinite recursion, right.
我们会不停地说然后我们就跑出来了
We're gonna keep saying, and
then we're gonna run out of stuff.
所以这里的这个点并不是一个超级的地方。
So the this dot here doesn't
work in place of a super.
这里不是多态的多态你跟我来
It's not a relative polymorphic
reference here, you follow me?
这不起作用，如果我们有这样的一个，我们如何去一个级别的原型链
It doesn't work, how do we go one level
up the prototype chain if we have a this
关键字， reference，如何从 deepJS 到 workshop.prototype?
keyword, reference, how do we go from
deepJS up to workshop.prototype?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你可以说， .
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well you could say,
.dondoproto.
唐多普托是这个属性的原型链中有一层
Dondoproto is the property, that goes
up one level of the prototype chain,
到车间里去
up to workshop.
但如果我说了这个我就会说
But if I said this .dondoproto.ask,
and then I called it.
这个关键词是什么 ?
What would it's this keyword be?
>> Kyle Simpson: 如果调用站点为 this.dunderproto.ask ，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If the call site
said this.dunderproto.ask, and
它在那里调用了一个方法，这个关键词点是什么呢 ?
it invoked a method there,
what would that this keyword point at?
>> 演讲者 3: 讲习班。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Workshop.
>> Kyle Simpson: Workshop.prototype，这不是我们想要的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Workshop.prototype,
which is not what we want.
因此，在第 11 行，我们必须做这一令人憎化的行为。
So instead on line 11,
we have to do this abomination.
此.dunderproto.ask.call此列。
This .dunderproto.ask.callthis.
我们发现了一个层次结构的原型链
We find the method one level
up the prototype chain but
我们必须在这方面援引它
we have to invoke it in our these context.
太可怕了吧
It's horrible, right?
我将此称为显式伪多态性。
I refer to this as explicit
pseudo polymorphism.
这太可怕了，这不是真正的相对多态性。
This is horrible,
this is not real relative polymorphism.
这不是超级关键词的立场
It's not a stand in for the super keyword.
顺便说下如果我们再贴另一个物体
And by the way, if we stuck
another object on the end of this,
比如我们把原型链扩大到一个层次
like if we extended our
prototype chain by one level.
现在我们不需要一个 .dunderproto
Now we don't need one
.dunderproto in there.
我们需要两个 deto protos
We need two dunder protos.
该函数必须指出，.dunderproto.dunderproto.ask.call到此。
That functions got to say this,
.dunderproto.dunderproto.ask.callthis.
如果加上第三个链接，我们需要三个 dettprotos。
And if we add a third link now
we need three dunder protos.
换句话说，当您在不使用类系统的情况下尝试影子时。
So in other words, when you try to
shadow without using the class system.
当你在原型机中尝试过影子时
When you were in prototypes and
you tried to shadow,
你最终造成了完全的破坏
you ended up creating essentially
this complete breakage.
没有办法做相对多态的多态性。
There's no way to do
the relative polymorphism.
为什么我们首先要为地球蒙上阴影 ?
Why on earth would we
shadow in the first place?
因为影像是你怎么做的，对吧 ?
Was because shadowing is how
you do polymorphism, right?
在阶级设计理论中，有一个子类的整个点是这样
In class design theory, the whole
point of having a child class is so
你可以继承父母的东西
that you can inherit
something from the parent.
覆盖它，然后调用 super 以访问它的父版本，以进行扩展。
Override it and then call super to access
the parent version of it, to extend it.
这就是我们在这里想做的事情。
So that's what we're trying to do here.
我们正在尝试覆盖和扩展 ASK 方法
We're trying to override and
extend the ASK method but
它不起作用，因为我们在一个系统的范围之外，
it doesn't work because we are outside
of the confines of a system that is very
通过鸭带精心设计的超级关键词
carefully constructed through duck tape,
a super keyword.